[
  {"index":1,"Question":"諦めないで","Answer":"Don't give up/ Hang in there."},
  {"index":2,"Question":"(\"sorry\"に)大丈夫だよ","Answer":"No worries."},
  {"index":3,"Question":"またしたいね","Answer":"We should do it again sometime"},
  {"index":4,"Question":"また来たいね","Answer":"We should come here again sometime"},
  {"index":5,"Question":"これにする","Answer":"I’llgo for this."},
  {"index":6,"Question":"いつも、四六時中","Answer":"all the time"},
  {"index":7,"Question":"何か心に留めとくことある？","Answer":"Is there anything I should keep in mind?"},
  {"index":8,"Question":"何か知っとくべきことある？","Answer":"Is there anything I should know?"},
  {"index":9,"Question":"3つ買ったら割引される","Answer":"You get a discount when you buy three."},
  {"index":10,"Question":"外食する余裕がない","Answer":"I can't afford to go out to dinner."},
  {"index":11,"Question":"夜ご飯食べに行かない？","Answer":"Wanna grab some dinner today?"},
  {"index":12,"Question":"確認なんだけど","Answer":"Just to confirm,"},
  {"index":13,"Question":"よくやった（若干上から）","Answer":"Good on you!"},
  {"index":14,"Question":"彼に聞いてみたらどう？","Answer":"Why don’t you ask him?"},
  {"index":15,"Question":"自分の仕事をしただけだよ","Answer":"Just doing my job."},
  {"index":16,"Question":"何か思いついたら連絡するね","Answer":"I'll text you when something comes up."},
  {"index":17,"Question":"大丈夫だよー（感謝・心配への返答）","Answer":"All good:)"},
  {"index":18,"Question":"やっちゃった、","Answer":"I messed up."},
  {"index":19,"Question":"このデザインは前のものよりも列が揃っている","Answer":"The columns in this design has more aligned than previous one"},
  {"index":20,"Question":"少し変だ","Answer":"It looks a bit weird."},
  {"index":21,"Question":"Johnnyという名前で予約しています","Answer":"I booked under the name of Johnny."},
  {"index":22,"Question":"もし良ければ","Answer":"If you prefer,"},
  {"index":23,"Question":"最近のことはよくわからないけど","Answer":"I’m not too sure about things lately, but..."},
  {"index":24,"Question":"6時頃に顔出すね","Answer":"I'll drop by around 6."},
  {"index":25,"Question":"関わらない方がいいよ","Answer":"You don't wanna get involved in this."},
  {"index":26,"Question":"いい意味でね","Answer":"I mean it in a good way."},
  {"index":27,"Question":"さらにいいね","Answer":"Even better"},
  {"index":28,"Question":"〇〇という表現は日常的に使われますか？","Answer":"Is the expression \"〇〇\" commonly used in daily life?"},
  {"index":29,"Question":"場所変える？","Answer":"You wanna switch places?"},
  {"index":30,"Question":"ネギ1束","Answer":"a bunch of green onion."},
  {"index":31,"Question":"個人的な問題だからほっといて","Answer":"Don't worry about me. It's a personal problem."},
  {"index":32,"Question":"今日しないといけないことがいっぱいある","Answer":"I have a bunch of things to do today"},
  {"index":33,"Question":"バナナ1房","Answer":"a bunch of bananas"},
  {"index":34,"Question":"前にも一回見た気がする","Answer":"I feel like I've seen it before."},
  {"index":35,"Question":"メモを見直す","Answer":"go over the notes."},
  {"index":36,"Question":"買い物すら行けない","Answer":"I can't even go shopping."},
  {"index":37,"Question":"何が起こってるの？","Answer":"What's going on?"},
  {"index":38,"Question":"友達を夕食に誘う","Answer":"I ask my friends out to dinner."},
  {"index":39,"Question":"私が面倒を見る","Answer":"I'll take care of it"},
  {"index":40,"Question":"もう行かなきゃ","Answer":"I have got to go now.(I gotta go now)"},
  {"index":41,"Question":"よくわからない","Answer":"I'm not quite sure."},
  {"index":42,"Question":"終電間に合った？","Answer":"Did you make the last train?"},
  {"index":43,"Question":"わからなかった","Answer":"What was it?/ I didn’t get it."},
  {"index":44,"Question":"共感できる","Answer":"I can relate to that."},
  {"index":45,"Question":"少し待っていただけますか？","Answer":"Do you mind waiting a moment?"},
  {"index":46,"Question":"うんざりだよ","Answer":"I'm sick of it."},
  {"index":47,"Question":"やってみます","Answer":"I’ll give it a try."},
  {"index":48,"Question":"そんなに重要じゃないよ。なんでもいいよ","Answer":"It doesn’t matter."},
  {"index":49,"Question":"何をお探しですか？","Answer":"What are you after?"},
  {"index":50,"Question":"知ってる知ってる","Answer":"I know, right?"},
  {"index":51,"Question":"場合によるかな","Answer":"It depends."},
  {"index":52,"Question":"もしそうなら(if)","Answer":"If that’s the case,"},
  {"index":53,"Question":"元気出して！","Answer":"snap out of it!"},
  {"index":54,"Question":"行くかどうか迷ってる","Answer":"I'm on the fence about going there."},
  {"index":55,"Question":"自分に失望した","Answer":"I'm disappointed in myself."},
  {"index":56,"Question":"お願いがあるんだけど","Answer":"Can you do me a favor?"},
  {"index":57,"Question":"そうは言いつつも","Answer":"Even so, "},
  {"index":58,"Question":"この女性大人っぽくてかっこいい","Answer":"She’s so mature and cool."},
  {"index":59,"Question":"明日どこかに行くつもりですか？","Answer":"Are you gonna go somewhere tomorrow?"},
  {"index":60,"Question":"ネット回線が繋がらない","Answer":"I can't connect to the internet."},
  {"index":61,"Question":"じゃがいも1袋","Answer":"a bag of potatoes"},
  {"index":62,"Question":"馬鹿げてる","Answer":"That's ridiculous"},
  {"index":63,"Question":"朝方の人間じゃない","Answer":"I'm not a morning person."},
  {"index":64,"Question":"ここから2駅だよ","Answer":"It's 2 stations away."},
  {"index":65,"Question":"もちろんです","Answer":"Absolutely"},
  {"index":66,"Question":"本当？マジで？","Answer":"Seriously? This is for real?"},
  {"index":67,"Question":"これ以上俺に近づかんといて","Answer":"Stay away from me anymore."},
  {"index":68,"Question":"誘いを断る","Answer":"turn down the offer"},
  {"index":69,"Question":"例えば、","Answer":"Let’s say"},
  {"index":70,"Question":"見てるだけです","Answer":"I'm just having a look."},
  {"index":71,"Question":"もううんざり、嫌だなぁ","Answer":"It's getting old. / This suck. / I’m over it."},
  {"index":72,"Question":"またねー","Answer":"I catch you later."},
  {"index":73,"Question":"できることはやった","Answer":"I did what I could."},
  {"index":74,"Question":"見逃したくない","Answer":"I don't want to miss it."},
  {"index":75,"Question":"全くわからなくてお手上げ","Answer":"That's over my head."},
  {"index":76,"Question":"気づいた？","Answer":"Did you pick up on it?"},
  {"index":77,"Question":"6時くらいでどう？","Answer":"What do you say about 6?"},
  {"index":78,"Question":"なんて言ったらいいかわからない","Answer":"What can I say?"},
  {"index":79,"Question":"店から出て行ってくれ","Answer":"I’m gonna have to ask you leave my store."},
  {"index":80,"Question":"手伝わせて","Answer":"Let me help you with that."},
  {"index":81,"Question":"その手もある","Answer":"That's the way to go."},
  {"index":82,"Question":"あいつどうしたん","Answer":"What's his problem."},
  {"index":83,"Question":"あなたが知っている人","Answer":"the man that you know of."},
  {"index":84,"Question":"本当のはずがない","Answer":"It can't be true."},
  {"index":85,"Question":"前のやつが好きやったなぁ","Answer":"I missed the old one."},
  {"index":86,"Question":"彼女はとても機嫌が悪い","Answer":"She is very crabby."},
  {"index":87,"Question":"まかせて","Answer":"Leave it to me"},
  {"index":88,"Question":"あなたを尊敬しています。","Answer":"I look up to you."},
  {"index":89,"Question":"ぜひ来てください","Answer":"Please come by all means"},
  {"index":90,"Question":"もう終わったことだ。","Answer":"It's water under the bridge."},
  {"index":91,"Question":"めっちゃ美味しい","Answer":"This tastes amazing!"},
  {"index":92,"Question":"お水はいかがですか？","Answer":"Would you like some water?"},
  {"index":93,"Question":"ちょっとかして","Answer":"give me."},
  {"index":94,"Question":"このままやらせよう","Answer":"Let him go."},
  {"index":95,"Question":"それいい感じだね","Answer":"That is nice touch."},
  {"index":96,"Question":"俺のことオーナーに告げ口した？","Answer":"Did you tell on me to the owner?"},
  {"index":97,"Question":"時間が残ってない","Answer":"There is not time left."},
  {"index":98,"Question":"カナダに行くの楽しみ","Answer":"I'm excited to go to Canada."},
  {"index":99,"Question":"あんまり美味しくない","Answer":"This isn't really my thing."},
  {"index":100,"Question":"まぁまぁかな","Answer":"Could be better. / Not bad, but not great."},
  {"index":101,"Question":"絶対に似合うよ","Answer":"I’m sure you look handsome in it."},
  {"index":102,"Question":"なんて呼べばいい？","Answer":"What should I call you?"},
  {"index":103,"Question":"何時が都合いい？","Answer":"What time is good for you?"},
  {"index":104,"Question":"素敵な家","Answer":"lovely house"},
  {"index":105,"Question":"ご不便をおかけしてすいません","Answer":"I'm sorry for the trouble / inconvenience."},
  {"index":106,"Question":"疲れてきた","Answer":"I'm getting tired."},
  {"index":107,"Question":"その時に決めよう","Answer":"let's play it by ear"},
  {"index":108,"Question":"今はお腹すいてないかな","Answer":"I'm good for now."},
  {"index":109,"Question":"疲れた","Answer":"I'm exhausted. / I'm feeling sluggish."},
  {"index":110,"Question":"それでOKです。","Answer":"That works for me."},
  {"index":111,"Question":"こちらへどうぞ","Answer":"Right this way."},
  {"index":112,"Question":"最悪","Answer":"This sucks."},
  {"index":113,"Question":"おすすめメニューありますか？","Answer":"What's good here? / What's your speciality?"},
  {"index":114,"Question":"その経験あるわ","Answer":"I've been there."},
  {"index":115,"Question":"2人でするのは？","Answer":"Let’s do something just two of us."},
  {"index":116,"Question":"会えてよかったよ","Answer":"It was great seeing you."},
  {"index":117,"Question":"ちょっと体調悪い","Answer":"I'm a bit sick. / I'm feeling under the weather."},
  {"index":118,"Question":"会えて嬉しい","Answer":"Pleasure to meet you."},
  {"index":119,"Question":"そういう意味じゃない","Answer":"I didn't mean to say that."},
  {"index":120,"Question":"どれくらい待ちますか？","Answer":"How long is the wait?"},
  {"index":121,"Question":"ごめん","Answer":"My apologies. / Sorry about that."},
  {"index":122,"Question":"俺は反対かな","Answer":"I don't agree with that idea."},
  {"index":123,"Question":"代わりにやってくれん？","Answer":"Would you do it in my place?"},
  {"index":124,"Question":"そうゆうことじゃなくて","Answer":"That's not what I mean."},
  {"index":125,"Question":"ちょっと買い物行ってくるわ","Answer":"I'm going to go out to get some stuff."},
  {"index":126,"Question":"お腹いっぱい","Answer":"I'm full. / I'm stuffed."},
  {"index":127,"Question":"済んだことは仕方がない","Answer":"What's done is done."},
  {"index":128,"Question":"久しぶり","Answer":"It's been a while / It's been a long time."},
  {"index":129,"Question":"今日は体調が悪い","Answer":"I'm feeling under the weather today."},
  {"index":130,"Question":"（あいづち）","Answer":"Fair enough. / That make sense."},
  {"index":131,"Question":"それじゃ全くダメだ","Answer":"That won’t do at all."},
  {"index":132,"Question":"後で言うわ","Answer":"I'll let you know later."},
  {"index":133,"Question":"これコーヒーに合うね","Answer":"This goes well with the coffee."},
  {"index":134,"Question":"いいね","Answer":"Genius."},
  {"index":135,"Question":"どういたしまして","Answer":"Anytime. / Don't mention it."},
  {"index":136,"Question":"私たちファッションの好み似てますね","Answer":"Your taste in fashion is the same as mine."},
  {"index":137,"Question":"最近どう？","Answer":"What's new? / How have you been?"},
  {"index":138,"Question":"そんな、悪いよ、","Answer":"I owe you one. / You don't have to."},
  {"index":139,"Question":"運試しをする","Answer":"I try my luck."},
  {"index":140,"Question":"お腹の調子が悪い","Answer":"My stomach's acting up."},
  {"index":141,"Question":"よし食べよう","Answer":"Let's dig it."},
  {"index":142,"Question":"着いたらすぐに連絡してください","Answer":"Please contact me as soon as you arrive there."},
  {"index":143,"Question":"お腹すいた","Answer":"I'm starving."},
  {"index":144,"Question":"そろそろ帰ろうかな","Answer":"I'm going to have to leave now."},
  {"index":145,"Question":"何か起こりそうな気がする。","Answer":"Something is going to happen."},
  {"index":146,"Question":"全く理解できない","Answer":"It doesn't make any sense."},
  {"index":147,"Question":"（準備なしに）とにかくやってみるよ","Answer":"I'll just wing it."},
  {"index":148,"Question":"ほんとそれ","Answer":"Tell me about it."},
  {"index":149,"Question":"知ってる限りではないなぁ","Answer":"Not that I know of."},
  {"index":150,"Question":"同じ考えだね","Answer":"We are on the same page."},
  {"index":151,"Question":"スケジュールが決まったら連絡ください。","Answer":"Please touch base with me once the schedule is decided."},
  {"index":152,"Question":"俺が悪かった","Answer":"My bad."},
  {"index":153,"Question":"超楽しみ","Answer":"I'm hyped."},
  {"index":154,"Question":"野球めっちゃ好きです","Answer":"I'm a big fan of baseball."},
  {"index":155,"Question":"まじそれな","Answer":"You can say that again"},
  {"index":156,"Question":"熱出てる","Answer":"I'm running a fever."},
  {"index":157,"Question":"お会計お願いします","Answer":"Can we get the bill? / Can we get the check? / Check, please."},
  {"index":158,"Question":"今仕事終わった","Answer":"Just got off work."},
  {"index":159,"Question":"ご飯食べた？","Answer":"Did you eat yet?"},
  {"index":160,"Question":"ありがとう","Answer":"I appreciate it."},
  {"index":161,"Question":"またね","Answer":"Catch you later. / Talk to you later."},
  {"index":162,"Question":"そうゆうこともあるよ","Answer":"It happens. / Things happen."},
  {"index":163,"Question":"体調ましになってきた","Answer":"I'm getting better. / I'm on the mend."},
  {"index":164,"Question":"今どこ？","Answer":"Where you at?"},
  {"index":165,"Question":"2人入れますか？","Answer":"Do you have a table for two? / two seats available today?"},
  {"index":166,"Question":"ちょっと遅れるわ","Answer":"I'll be a little bit late."},
  {"index":167,"Question":"機会を逃した","Answer":"I missed the chance. /I missed the boat."},
  {"index":168,"Question":"それ何の意味があるん？","Answer":"What's the point of doing it."},
  {"index":169,"Question":"6時にしようか","Answer":"Let's do 6."},
  {"index":170,"Question":"一緒にやるのはどう？","Answer":"How about we do it together?"},
  {"index":171,"Question":"サボるな","Answer":"Don't cut corners."},
  {"index":172,"Question":"気にすんな","Answer":"Don't worry."},
  {"index":173,"Question":"飲み行く？","Answer":"Wanna grab a drink?"},
  {"index":174,"Question":"注文いいですか？","Answer":"I think we're ready. / We're ready to order."},
  {"index":175,"Question":"簡単、余裕","Answer":"Piece of cake."},
  {"index":176,"Question":"待たせてごめん","Answer":"Sorry for the wait."},
  {"index":177,"Question":"元気？/元気！","Answer":"How's it going? / Pretty good. How are you?"},
  {"index":178,"Question":"奢るよ","Answer":"It's on me. / I got it, don't worry."},
  {"index":179,"Question":"体を鍛えてる","Answer":"I’m getting in shape"},
  {"index":180,"Question":"今さっき明日面接を受けることになった。","Answer":"I just got scheduled for an interview tomorrow."},
  {"index":181,"Question":"彼女がだんだん可愛く見えてきた","Answer":"She’s starting to look cute to me."},
  {"index":182,"Question":"応援してて","Answer":"Wish me luck!"},
  {"index":183,"Question":"彼女の演技上手くなってる","Answer":"Her acting has improved."},
  {"index":184,"Question":"痛そう","Answer":"It looks so painful."},
  {"index":185,"Question":"味だけでアールグレイってわかるの？","Answer":"Can you tell it's Earl Grey just by the taste?"},
  {"index":186,"Question":"最後までやり切りたい","Answer":"I wanna see it through."},
  {"index":187,"Question":"机の上を片付ける","Answer":"Clean up the desk."},
  {"index":188,"Question":"彼は脚を打たれた","Answer":"He got shot in the leg."},
  {"index":189,"Question":"全く同感だよ","Answer":"I can't agree more."},
  {"index":190,"Question":"もう終わったこと","Answer":"What is done is done."},
  {"index":191,"Question":"そんな気分じゃない","Answer":"I'm not in the mood."},
  {"index":192,"Question":"ちょっとやりすぎ","Answer":"That’s a bit much."},
  {"index":193,"Question":"念の為に言っとくけど","Answer":"Just so you know."},
  {"index":194,"Question":"気が変わった","Answer":"I changed my mind."},
  {"index":195,"Question":"めんどくさいな","Answer":"What a hassle."},
  {"index":196,"Question":"後で連絡するね(get)","Answer":"I'll get back to you."},
  {"index":197,"Question":"仕方ないね","Answer":"It is what it is."},
  {"index":198,"Question":"ちょっと様子見よう","Answer":"Let’s wait and see."},
  {"index":199,"Question":"それありかも","Answer":"That might work."},
  {"index":200,"Question":"どっちでもいいよ","Answer":"Either is fine."},
  {"index":201,"Question":"そんな感じのやつ","Answer":"Something like that."},
  {"index":202,"Question":"正直言って","Answer":"To be honest."},
  {"index":203,"Question":"急いでないよ","Answer":"No rush."},
  {"index":204,"Question":"どうでもいい","Answer":"I couldn’t care less."},
  {"index":205,"Question":"ちょっと考えさせて","Answer":"Let me think about this."},
  {"index":206,"Question":"まぁそんなとこ","Answer":"Close enough"},
  {"index":207,"Question":"一般的に","Answer":"as a general rule"},
  {"index":208,"Question":"全体的にいって","Answer":"by and large"},
  {"index":209,"Question":"結果として","Answer":"as a result"},
  {"index":210,"Question":"大部分では","Answer":"for the most part"},
  {"index":211,"Question":"言いたいことはわかる","Answer":"I get your point,"},
  {"index":212,"Question":"やっぱりこっちにしようかな","Answer":"On the second thought, I think I’ll have this."},
  {"index":213,"Question":"これに勝るものはないね","Answer":"There’s nothing like this."},
  {"index":214,"Question":"その調子でね","Answer":"Keep it up."},
  {"index":215,"Question":"相変わらずだよ","Answer":"Same as always."},
  {"index":216,"Question":"V できる状態じゃない","Answer":"You’re in no condition to do V"},
  {"index":217,"Question":"本気で言ってる？","Answer":"You really mean that?"},
  {"index":218,"Question":"突っ立ってないで","Answer":"Instead of standing there."},
  {"index":219,"Question":"一口飲む？","Answer":"Would you like a sip?"},
  {"index":220,"Question":"大したことじゃないよ","Answer":"It's not a big deal."},
  {"index":221,"Question":"時が経つにつれて","Answer":"as time marched on "},
  {"index":222,"Question":"でもありがとう","Answer":"Thank you though."},
  {"index":223,"Question":"今にわかる、見てたらわかる","Answer":"You’ll see it."},
  {"index":224,"Question":"本当に好きだったのね","Answer":"You sure did like it."}
]